// creating an array and passing the question number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is considered the King of Pop?",
    answer: "Michael Jackson",
    options: [
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Elvis Presley",
      "Michael Jackson",
      "Frank Sinatra"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which famous ballet features a young girl who dreams of a prince and a magical adventure?",
    answer: "The Nutcracker",
    options: [
      "The Sleeping Beauty",
      "Swan Lake",
      "Cinderella",
      "The Nutcracker"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which famous comedian is known for his role in the sitcom Seinfeld?",
    answer: "Jerry Seinfeld",
    options: [
      "Robin Williams",
      "Jerry Seinfeld",
      "Chris Rock",
      "Eddie Murphy"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the name of the world's most famous opera house located in Milan, Italy?",
    answer: "La Scala",
    options: [
      "Sydney Opera House",
      "La Scala",
      "Royal Opera House",
      "Palais Garnier"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which music genre originated in the African-American communities of New Orleans, USA?",
    answer: "Jazz",
    options: [
      "Jazz",
      "Country",
      "Hip-hop",
      "Reggae"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who is the playwright of the tragedy Romeo and Juliet?",
    answer: "William Shakespeare",
    options: [
      "William Shakespeare",
      "Arthur Miller",
      "Tennessee Williams",
      "Oscar Wilde"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What famous choreographer is known for his unique style, blending jazz and burlesque in his works?",
    answer: "Bob Fosse",
    options: [
      "Martha Graham",
      "Bob Fosse",
      "George Balanchine",
      "Twyla Tharp"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which legendary rock band is known for the hit songs Bohemian Rhapsody and We Will Rock You?",
    answer: "Queen",
    options: [
      "The Rolling Stones",
      "Led Zeppelin",
      "Queen",
      "The Beatles"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which dance style originated in Argentina and is known for its passion and dramatic flair?",
    answer: "Tango",
    options: [
      "Salsa",
      "Tango",
      "Ballet",
      "Hip-hop"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What musical instrument is known for its versatility and is often called the king of instruments?",
    answer: "Piano",
    options: [
      "Piano",
      "Violin",
      "Trumpet",
      "Flute"
    ]
  },
];